frontporch.com 2014-02-21

# Privacy Policy In-Browser Notifications by Front Porch - Network Based Messaging for Cable, Telco, Mobile, and Wi-Fi Broadband Networks, Hotspot 2.0 Passpoint Branding Monetization

## **Effective Date:  October 19, 2010**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) applies to the www.frontporch.com web site.  It tells users (“you”) about the web site, the information that Front Porch, Inc. collects through this web site, and how Front Porch, Inc. uses and shares this information.

#### **Types of Information We Collect**

Front Porch, Inc. collects both “personally identifiable information” and “non-personally identifiable information” from or about users of our web site.

_**Personally Identifiable Information**  
_Front Porch, Inc. collects several types of information that may identify a particular individual (“personally identifiable information”) when you provide it to us through your use of the site, such as by submitting a contact form inquiry, application for employment, or using other tools and services provided on the web site.  The types of personally identifiable information you may provide include your name and contact information such as your phone number and email address, and information about your preferences.

_**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
_We may also collect non-personally identifiable information when you access our site.  Non-personally identifiable information is anonymous information that is not associated with a specific individual.  The types of non-personally identifiable information that we collect include information about how you access the Internet and our site; your IP address, browser type, and Internet connection; and information about how you choose to use the site. We may use this information or share it with our service providers and other third parties for various reasons, such as improving the web site. ****

#### How We Use Personally Identifiable Information

Front Porch, Inc. uses the personally identifiable information you provide to us through this site in order to respond to your requests or serve you better.  For example, we may provide you with customer support; verify or review your registration information; communicate with you about products or services that may be of interest to you from us, our marketing partners, or other third parties; respond to your requests or inquiries; or enforce our terms and conditions.

#### Sharing Your Personally Identifiable Information

****Front Porch, Inc. may share your personally identifiable information with vendors and service providers that carry out activities on our behalf.   We may also share your personally identifiable information with selected third parties with whom we have a business relationship for their own marketing purposes.  You may request that your personally identifiable information not be shared with third parties for marketing purposes by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address, to Front Porch, Inc. using the contact information below.

Any third parties with whom we share personally identifiable information may have their own policies which describe how they use and disclose your information.  Those policies will govern the use, handling, and disclosure of your information once we have transferred or shared it with those third parties as described in this Policy or our Terms and Conditions.

Front Porch, Inc. may disclose your personally identifiable information in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required or permitted by law.  We may disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe disclosure is necessary to prevent or take action regarding suspected illegal activity, fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect or defend our company, our employees, our web site users, or others; or to enforce our agreements or policies.In addition, in the unlikely event that all or substantially all of Front Porch, Inc.’s stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, or that Front Porch, Inc. is merged into or combined with another company, Front Porch, Inc. may transfer your information to the acquiring entity or to the transferee entity.

#### Links to Third Party Web Sites

We may provide links or automatically redirect you to third party web sites that do not operate under this Policy.  We are not responsible for the policies and practices of these third parties, and we do not monitor or control their information practices.  You should consult the privacy policies of these other sites to learn how your privacy is protected.  On occasion, these third party web sites may provide us with information about your use of their sites.

#### Children’s Privacy

****Our web site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.   We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

#### Security

****Front Porch, Inc. has put in place reasonable physical, administrative and technical security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to the information we collect online.   However, no web site or data system can be completely secure.  Although we take reasonable steps to secure your information, we do not guarantee and you should not expect that your personal information, searches, or other communications will always remain secure.

#### Website Publisher’s Choice

As the owner or the webmaster of a domain, you can determine if Internet provider messages to their subscribers can be served alongside your content. To learn more or activate that choice, click here.

#### Changes to this Policy

Front Porch, Inc. may modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  Changes to this Policy will be posted on the Front Porch, Inc. web site and we will revise the “effective date” at the top of this Policy.

#### California Residents’ Privacy Rights

****California residents, like all Front Porch, Inc. web site users, may request that their personally identifiable information not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes by sending your request, including your full name, email address and postal address, to Front Porch, Inc. using the contact information below.   California residents are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, Suite 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).

#### Contact

If you have questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please write to us:

Front Porch, Inc.  
14520 Mono Way, Suite 200  
Sonora, CA 95370
